

Yury Kastsen

- +48881096343
- spkava@gmail.com
- Wrocław

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kastsen

Website: https://mental.gatsbyjs.io
Github: https://github.com/kastsen

Introduction

I assist clients in bringing their concepts to life, ensuring projects are launched on time. Programming, team management, and product support and enhancement all fall within my scope of responsibilities.

My technology stack includes: JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Node.js, Webpack, Pixi.js, Create.js, Three.js, Gatsby.js, HTML5, Pug.js, CSS3, SCSS, Bash, Git and more.

I'm now looking forward to using my skills and experience in a fulfilling position.

Experience

12/2022 - until now

Web Games Developer

OS Games

Web Games Development and maintenance service:

- · CORAL ISLE 2 https://coralisle2.quartsoft.com/index.html
- · FARLAND https://farland.guartsoft.com/index.html
- · PAPAYA https://papaya.quartsoft.com/index.html
- \cdot Skills: JavaScript \cdot Typescript \cdot Webpack \cdot Pixi JS \cdot Create JS \cdot React \cdot Redux \cdot HTML5 \cdot Git \cdot mySQL \cdot REST API

03/2020 - 08/2022

Playable Ads Developer

Vizor Games

Playable ads development. Framework development and support. Build automatisation. Optimization of processes and tasks, work with the team. Skills: Node.js \cdot npm \cdot Webpack \cdot JavaScript \cdot Matter JS \cdot Bash \cdot Pixi.js \cdot Spine Animations \cdot Tiled \cdot HTML5 \cdot SVN \cdot JSON \cdot ES6+

12/2019 - 03/2020

Front-end Developer

Bamboo Apps

Project support and maintenance service. Interviews, onboarding for new employees. Skills: JavaScript · Node.js · Express.js · mySQL · CSS3 · SCSS · SPA · UI · Github · Webpack · Git · SASS · AJAX · Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

· npm · ES6+ · API · Pug.js

05/2019 - 05/2020 Front-end Development Speaker

School MyFreedomIT

Skills: Public Speaking · CSS3 · HTML5 · Git · Bootstrap · JavaScript

02/2018 - 11/2019 Front-end Developer

Logic Software Inc.

Work with a team, including a team of designers, developers and marketing. June training. Support and optimization of the project. Skills: Node.js \cdot JavaScript \cdot CSS3 \cdot SCSS \cdot React \cdot Web Design \cdot Agile Methodologies \cdot Scrum \cdot UX \cdot jQuery \cdot Webpack \cdot Git \cdot SASS \cdot AJAX \cdot JSX \cdot Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) \cdot JSON \cdot npm \cdot Yarn \cdot ES6+ \cdot API \cdot PHP \cdot mySQL

06/2015 - 12/2017 Web Development Specialist

inAweb

Web sites design, development and support. Building custom WordPress themes and plugins.

05/2012 - 08/2014 Content management, HTML-markup

Daily News Portal

Content management, web-administrator, HTML-markup.

Knowledge and skills

Languages:

Byelorussian (proficient) Russian (proficient) English (intermediate) Polish (pre-intermediate)

Czech (pre-intermediate)

Skills:



Education

Level of education

University

2015 - 2016

Erasmus+ EVS
Politologie

2008 - 2012

BSPU
Philology. Journalism

Certification and courses

2019 **School MyfreedomIT** Javascript, React JS. Front-end Development

2013 Používání vizuálních symbolů a tvůrčích přístupů

Prague

Známost s českou zkušeností v použití vizuálních symbolů a kreativních

přístupů k sociální činnosti.

Hobbies

Music Nature Quad roller skating